<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>COMP1101</title><link>https://cs.tescobank.pro/</link><description>Recent content on COMP1101</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><atom:link href="https://cs.tescobank.pro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Education</title><link>https://cs.tescobank.pro/education/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cs.tescobank.pro/education/</guid><description>Cloud Technologies in Education Ways cloud technology improved the quality of learning Purpose of Computers in Education Computers are one of the most valuable resources in a classroom because they serve so many useful functions. With computers and the internet, students today have a wealth of information at their fingertips that can help them develop their research and communication skills while preparing them for a future career in a workforce that is increasingly reliant on computer technology.</description></item><item><title>Protein Modelling</title><link>https://cs.tescobank.pro/protein_modelling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cs.tescobank.pro/protein_modelling/</guid><description>Protein Modelling For research and diagnosis of genetic diseases What is Protein Modelling? Protein modelling, or more specifically, protein structure prediction is an essential field of research and development that aims to predict the structure of folded proteins. It is used to aid research on the biological functionality of proteins and even to help diagnose and potentially treat genetic diseases like:
Altzheimer's Parkinson's Huntington's Cystic Fibrosis Protein folding is a complex cellular process that folds proteins into specific 3D shapes.</description></item><item><title>The World Wide Web</title><link>https://cs.tescobank.pro/www/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cs.tescobank.pro/www/</guid><description>The World Wide Web The world wide web has revolutionised society with unparalelled information sharing and communication speed. Never before was it possible to send information from London to New York in a matter of seconds
allowing for greater collaberation between geographic locations and faster sharing of technoloigies
Use cases: Transfer of financial data Social communication Technology sharing How it works:
A system of hypertext documents (HTML) are interlinked together through the internet, allowing for the</description></item><item><title>Wearable Technology</title><link>https://cs.tescobank.pro/wearable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cs.tescobank.pro/wearable/</guid><description>Wearable Technology in Healthcare Wearable tech for the visually impaired Researchers have created a wearable computer to aid the blind, and help reduce collision risk. The computer consists of a small mainboard and several cameras which allow it to detect objects around the wearer, when used in conjunction with a guide dog, it is reportedly 40% effective at preventing collisions (source) This device can also be beneficial to those who cannot afford the expense of a guide dog, which can cost up to $60,000 Upon detection of a collision hazard, one of the two bluetooth enabled wristbands that the user wears will vibrate, indicating which direction the object is in Photo courtesy of Mass Eye and Ear Wearable tech for health monitoring Many people now own a smart watch, the capabilities of which are ever expanding.</description></item></channel></rss>