<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>COMP1101</title><link>https://cs.tescobank.pro/</link><description>Recent content on COMP1101</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><atom:link href="https://cs.tescobank.pro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Education</title><link>https://cs.tescobank.pro/education/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cs.tescobank.pro/education/</guid><description>Computing Used for Education "Computers are one of the most valuable resources in a classroom because they serve so many useful functions. With computers and the internet, students today have a wealth of information at their fingertips that can help them develop their research and communication skills while preparing them for a future career in a workforce that is increasingly reliant on computer technology." Source: theclassroom.com
The most common usage of computer for education are:</description></item><item><title>Protein Modelling</title><link>https://cs.tescobank.pro/protein_modelling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cs.tescobank.pro/protein_modelling/</guid><description>Protein Modelling Predicting protein structures for research and diagnosis of genetic diseases What is Protein Modelling? Protein modelling, or more specifically, protein structure prediction is an essential field of research and development that aims to predict the structure of folded proteins. It is used to aid research on the biological functionality of proteins and even to help diagnose and potentially treat genetic diseases like:</description></item><item><title>The World Wide Web</title><link>https://cs.tescobank.pro/www/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cs.tescobank.pro/www/</guid><description>The World Wide Web
The world wide web has revolutionised society with unparalelled information sharing and communication speed. Never before was it possible to send information from London to New York in a matter of seconds
allowing for greater collaberation between geographic locations and faster sharing of technoloigies
Use cases: Social communication Transfer of financial data Technology sharing How it works:
A system of hypertext documents (HTML) are interlinked together through the internet, allowing for the</description></item></channel></rss>